import IQuestion, { QuestionType } from "../entity/Question";

const QuestionDataPart6 : IQuestion[] = [{
    id: 'p6_1131',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '131',
    answer: ['will donate', 'donated', 'might donate', 'donating'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p6_1132',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '132',
    answer: ['museum', 'hotel', 'factory', 'store'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
},{
    id: 'p6_1133',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '133',
    answer: ['Despite', 'Over', 'Between', 'Beneath'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
},{
    id: 'p6_1134',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '134',
    answer: ['The opening ceremony will begin at 10:00 A.M.', 'The community center offers classes for adults and children.', 'Last night’s event was the most successful thus far.', 'Mr. Munrow plans to open a new location in London next year.'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
},{
    id: 'p6_1135',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '135',
    answer: ['concerts', 'discussions', 'programming', 'development'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
},{
    id: 'p6_1136',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '1136',
    answer: ['offers', 'offering', 'will offer', 'have offered'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
},{
    id: 'p6_1137',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '137',
    answer: ['We plan to merge with another local radio station next year.', 'You can even meet some of your favorite broadcasters.', 'This is the first event in our February schedule.', 'This station continues to be a vital part of your community.'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
},{
    id: 'p6_1138',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '138',
    answer: ['special', 'specialize', 'especially', 'specialization'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
},{
    id: 'p6_1139',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '139',
    answer: ['to develop', 'will develop', 'has developed', 'could have developed'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
},{
    id: 'p6_1140',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '140',
    answer: ['economic', 'unforeseen', 'volunteer', 'frequent'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
},{
    id: 'p6_1141',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '141',
    answer: ['While the city is anxious for work to get underway, delays are typical for major commercial endeavors ', 
    'Nearby tenants, however, have raised some valid concerns about the construction noise.', 
    'Despite city officials’ promises to grant the company a long-term agreement, they now may have to reconsider.',
     'Council members will vote on three different proposals from the architects.'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
},{
    id: 'p6_1142',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '142',
    answer: ['argument', 
    'background', 
    'estimate',
    'combination'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
},{
    id: 'p6_1143',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '143',
    answer: ['Now', 
    'Afterward', 
    'Then',
    'Meanwhile'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
},{
    id: 'p6_1144',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '144',
    answer: ['To place a subscription, call our service desk during business hours.', 
    'If you do not receive your copy in a week, please contact us immediately.', 
    'Artists are invited to submit descriptions of their work.',
    'The first concert is scheduled to take place in Vancouver in early October'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
},{
    id: 'p6_1145',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '145',
    answer: ['accessing', 
    'accesses', 
    'accessed',
    'access'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
},{
    id: 'p6_1146',
    type: QuestionType.part6,
    question: '146',
    answer: ['for', 
    'about', 
    'on',
    'at'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
}];

export default QuestionDataPart6;
